{
    "subject": "resource/Sana_Safi",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kabul",
    "human_readable": "Sana Safi was born in Kabul.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9584987759590149,
            "question": "Is Sana Safi from Kabul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8970284461975098,
            "question": "Where was Sana Safi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8380783796310425,
            "question": "Has Sana Safi lived in other places besides Kabul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8274915814399719,
            "question": "When was Sana Safi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637803912162781,
            "question": "Where did Sana Safi grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6483447551727295,
            "question": "What is the name of Sana Safi's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5669686794281006,
            "question": "What is Sana Safi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3661055862903595,
            "question": "What is Kabul known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.331141859292984,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Sana Safi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30266064405441284,
            "question": "Does Sana Safi have any notable achievements?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sana Safi was born in Kabul.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8461_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Sana Safi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8461_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Kabul known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8461_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sana Safi known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8461_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8461_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Sana Safi was born in Kabul,\" which directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}